Previously on Reacher...
Susan Duffy, meet Angel Doll.
Thanks for the hand, Angel Doll.
- McCabe's the one who kidnapped you?\N- Yeah.
You ever hear McCabe or your dad\Nuse the name Xavier Quinn?
Not that I can remember.
Beck confirmed McCabe\Nis running this whole thing.
That's got to be\NJulius McCabe, right?
I know him as Xavier Quinn.
The guy you thought was dead?
The guy I thought I killed.\NHow's the bodyguard?
We patched him up,\Ntook a few runs at him,
- but he's not saying shit.\N-  Got a call from McCabe.
He sent someone over to Bizarre Bazaar\Nto get Angel Doll's laptop back,
because it had a tracking app on it\Nin case it was lost or stolen.
Here's the address.
Anyone inside ain't supposed to be?\NWe kill them.
-  Yeah?\N- Eliot, is Duffy with you?
- Uh, no.\N-  Come on, man,
I want to play the Feud.
Come on... hey, asshole!
She and Villanueva left me here\Nto babysit again
while they check out some lead.
A rug and tubing facility.
Why? Everything okay?
Quinn's men are looking\Nfor Angel Doll's laptop.
They'll be on them any minute,\Nand no one's answering their phones.
Shit. I-I'll look up the name\Nof the company and call them.
Get it done.
It's like every 20 minutes with you.
Get that thing checked.
I did.
They put me on the Flomax\Nand the what-do-you-call-it?
The saw palmetto.
Well, up your dosage.
I'd rather not talk about this.
I'd rather not be constantly held up\Nby your mango-sized prostate.
Why would someone be\Ncalling here when it's closed?
Maybe leaving a message.
It's a commercial shop.
People don't just pop in here to buy shit.
You do business with this place,\Nyou know the hours.
Our cells don't work in here.
Something's off. I'm answering.
Tubing.
Get out of there now.\NQuinn sent people over.
We got to move or we're dead.
He's the last one.
It'll look suspicious if there's\Nanother ambush and I'm the only survivor.
Head to the south exit.
When you get close,\Nyell for Villanueva to follow.
I'll make sure you get out.
They're tracking Angel Doll's laptop.\NWhere is it?
In the car.
When you drive away,\Nthrow it out the window.
Go.
South exit. Let's get out of here!
Shit.
Get rid of it!
Get in.
Who the fuck are you?
Duke's replacement.
Go!
Tires are stuck.
- We're gonna have to push her out.\N- Goddamn it.
Our competitors don't hire\Nwomen and old guys.
And one of them had a Glock 26 Gen3.
Those are government issued.
I'm telling you, these are federal agents.
Okay.
Cop--
Jesus.
Boss is pissed like a copperhead.\NThis ain't good.
This ain't good at all.
Salud.
What are we celebrating here?
After today? How about breathing?
We didn't find Teresa.\NWe should still be looking.
I get it, and we will.
- But I also need you to be...\N- To be what?
- Nothing.\N- Say it.
I'm not saying shit.
Remember that Menjivar kid?
Four years old,\Ndisappeared from his backyard,
everyone figured some chomo did him in.
Mija, this is a different kind of case.
Bullshit. Missing's missing.
No one in Boston PD thought\Nthat kid was coming home
in anything other than a box.
By Thanksgiving,\Nthe news stopped covering it,
the parents gave up,
had a funeral with an empty coffin\Nat St. Joachim's,
then what happens?
Connor Lafferty.
Old man fucking Lafferty walks\Nlittle Marco Menjivar
right into Salesbury's for an ice cream,\Nlike any other day.
I still remember the order:
rocky road and a Diet Dr Pepper.
This isn't a case of some sweet\Nold man with Alzheimer's
that took a kid home\Nthinking it was his grandson.
The guys that grabbed Teresa\Nare major league.
My point is, odds get beat.
Marco Menjivar was\Nmissing for nine months.
Statistics said his body was\Nrotting in a landfill or an oil drum,
and he wasn't even hurt!
He was fed, he watched cartoons,\Ngot taken care of.
Now he's 14, hardly remembers it,
kid was all-county wide receiver
- last season.\N- Tight end.
All I'm saying is that good shit\Ncan still happen.
So either stay on board and believe\Nsome of the good is coming our way,
believe that odds get beat,\Nor shut up about it.
Okay.
Let's get back to work.
Fuck.
Hey, Paulie.
We got a little "Neptune Society"\Nthing going on.
You want to give us a hand?
Okay, then.
Pick him up, tough guy.
There we go.
I threw a living, breathing guy\Ndown here once.
Paulie broke his spine.
Poor bastard couldn't walk.
While we were waiting for the wave,
he was begging me to shoot him\Ninstead of letting him drown.
What'd you do?
I let him drown.
Bombs away.
Hey, yo! Look at that. Nature's toilet.
Tide comes in strongest this time of day.
Pulls everything in that cove\Nout like a vacuum.
Undertow's brutal.
Let's go get the other one.
You don't seem to be too broken up\Nabout your pals getting killed.
They ain't my pals. They're cannon fodder.
Warm bodies to do the things\NMcCabe needs done when he needs them done.
He pulls them in from all over...
dishonorable discharges from the service,
guys tossed from the police academy\Nfor failing the psych eval, ex-cons,
the chronically antisocial and unhirable.
No offense.
What category do you fall into?
I'm like Tony Soprano.
I'm in waste management.
That shit never gets old.
What will you do if the tide\Ndoesn't clean up your mess?
These rips could pull\Na Clydesdale out to sea.
I know these currents\Nlike the back of my hand.
Speaking of the back of your hand,\NI just realized who you are.
Duke told me about you.
You're the one that made Paulie\Nknock himself out.
Not out. Just down.
Either way, Paulie's gonna fuck you up.
Better be careful.
Why do you give a shit?
I don't.
I just don't want to have\Nto drag your big ass down here.
It's not like I get paid by the pound.
Reacher.
Yeah. You guys okay?
We're good.
Thanks for saving my ass today.
I owe you.
Saving the life of a good person\Nis a pretty low bar for praise.
Next moves?
Villy's back at the cabin getting his car.
We're gonna split up to cover more ground,
check on some of the addresses\Nfrom Angel Doll's laptop.
You wrote 'em down?
Why would I do that?\NThey were on a laptop.
Good point.
No, we remembered about five of them.
I'm gonna hit a place\Nthat makes storage crates.
Figure they use them to move the rugs.
Villy's gonna run down\Nsome kind of industrial lubricant plant.
I have no idea what that's for,\Nbut from what I could find online,
it looks like a legit operation that Quinn\Nmight buy product from, for some reason.
His guys could be waiting for you
now that Quinn knows\NFeds are snooping around.
We've got no choice.
Their location's been compromised,\Nso they'll have to move Teresa.
If we're lucky,\Nmaybe we catch 'em in the act.
And if we do, I'm taking 'em out.
Sounds like a plan.
- Anything else?\N- Yeah.
I have your badge.
Shit. I didn't notice I'd lost it.
Uh, give it back to me\Nnext time I see you.
Reacher!
I got to go.
Reacher, where the hell are you?
What the hell were you doing behind there?
Had to take a piss.
I have nine bathrooms inside this house.
Yeah, but I was outside.
I just got a call from McCabe.\NWere those guys really Feds?
Not sure.\NHarley got a better look than I did.
Well, McCabe sent\Ntwo of his men over here.
- They're in the kitchen now.\N- It's your house.
- If you don't like it, tell them to leave.\N- It doesn't work that way.
McCabe isn't screwing around.
First, the Angel Doll bullshit,\Nand now these Feds.
He's on edge and pissed.\NTwo things you don't want that guy to be.
You're my head of security.\NDo your fucking job.
Heard things been tough lately.
Don't worry, princess.
Cavalry's here.
Hot as hell, black as pitch.
Thank you.
You like the coffee?
It's okay.
It's from a feline's asshole.
Some posh brand Zachary likes.
They feed coffee beans to cats,
then dig through the litter box\Nafter they pass 'em through.
What for?
Something in their digestive system\Nimproves the taste.
It tastes like coffee.
Might want to leave the cat out of it.
You owe me 20 bucks.
I told you. He don't like pussy.
Speaking of pussy,
I've never been so jealous\Nof a fork in my life.
You like cream?
- I know where you can get some more.\N-  Mm-hmm.
Oui, de ta mère.
What did she say?
She said the cream came from your mother.
Probably 'cause she's a big fat cow.
So she's funny now?
You have any thoughts on dessert?
No, man.
I got diabetes.
A cat's asshole?
Hey, brother?
Can you take these cuffs off?
They're killing me, man.
Absolutely not.
Oh, come on, man.
They're killing me.
Oh, I mean, my wrists\Nhaven't hurt this bad
since I was 13 and I found\Nmy uncle's Elle MacPherson Playboy.
Jesus Christ.
Hey, look, man,\Nwe've been hanging out for days.
Watching TV,\Nshooting the shit like regular guys.
But then you got to feed me chow mein\Nlike I'm a baby bird.
It's fucking humiliating.
If you're not gonna let me\Neat like a regular guy and
just like take a break off these cuffs,
least you could do\Nis let me have a Chesterfield.
I told you there are regulations.
Come on, man.
None of me being here follows regulations.
- I hate the smoke.\N- Crack a window.
All it's gonna do is\Ntake seven minutes of my life, not yours.
Come on, brah.
Front right jacket pocket.
Come on, do me a solid.
Please.
Only once.
All right.
And I never want to hear\Nabout a fucking cigarette ever again.
One time.
Make it count.
Understood?
Thanks for the smoke.
I hope you got good news.
Sounds like\Nit's the same as yours.
Those places were a waste of time.
Where are you now?
Stopped to gas up.
You're gassy enough.
Drop whatever's left\Nof whatever you're eating.
I'll order you a salad at the cabin.
Steven.
Steven! Steven?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! Steven?
Steven?
Fuck!
No way you'd risk getting me killed
by calling unless it was\Nsomething really important.
Eliot's dead and the bodyguard's gone.
You got to get out of the there.
By now he already told Beck\Nthe kidnapping attempt was a fake.
If he had, Paulie would be up here\Nright now tearing my head off.
Does Cooper have his phone?
No, it was locked in the other room.
Uh, I'm guessing he just ran\Nout of here soon as he could.
Then he can't call Beck.
Well, he can go to a bar, use their phone.
You said Beck's number was unlisted.
How many numbers do you have memorized?
His only play is coming here in person.
How much time do I have?
I don't know...
Wait!
Wait, uh...
His smartwatch says\Nthat his heart rate spiked
and then stopped...
ten minutes ago.
Where's Villanueva?
He's headed back here.
Okay.
I'm gonna need his help\Nif I'm gonna intercept
the bodyguard before he gets to the house.
What-what reason\Nare you gonna give Beck for leaving?
I'm not gonna give it to him.
You are.
Reacher?
Get to the blind turn that leads\Nto Beck's house.
Pull over 40 yards south\Nand empty the car.
Make it as light as possible.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
What the hell's going on?
Bodyguard killed Eliot.
If you don't do exactly as I say,
the kid'll have died for nothing.
That's a big boy.
The landlines are all out, too.
What the hell is going on?
Someone must've cut the power.
Who?
Maybe the guys\NAngel Doll was working with.
We've killed a bunch of their people\Nin the past 24 hours.
Could be retribution.
Might be coming after your son.
Electric's down all over the property.
The gates open by default\Nwhen there's a power outage.
It's open?
Well, who the hell's watching it?
One of the new guys McCabe sent.
Well, get down there with them.\NWe might be going to war.
Fuck off. You ain't my boss.
No, McCabe is.
And you want to see what he'll do to you\Nif his operation is wiped out
and you're not at your post?
Okay, look,
I'm gonna go to the end of the road\Nthat leads to the property.
It's the only way in or out of here.
If anyone thinks they're coming in,\Nthey're gonna have to go through me first.
What's happening?
Go back to your room and lock the door.\NEverything will be fine.
No, Richard, come on down here with me.\NI'll keep an eye on you.
He's safer upstairs.
I want him where I can see him.
Richard, do what I say.
I don't know. It just happened\Na few minutes ago.
Well, I-I don't really think\Nthat's necessary, but...
All right.
Got it.
I'll do it now.
McCabe wants\Nthe entire staff searched.
Maid, cook, groundskeeper.
Grab the mechanic, too.\NToss all their rooms.
If there's another rat,\NMcCabe wants it caught.
Let's go.
- Get out of bed.
- Get out now. Let's go, come on.
- Get off me! What the hell is going on?\N- Downstairs.
- Downstairs now. Yeah, you too.\N- Get downstairs.
- Get down there.\N- For God's sake.
Now. Move your asses.
We don't have much time.
- Pull your car to the middle of the road.\N- Why?
We're gonna flip it over.
Of course we are.
Follow me.
We'll use the slope to our advantage.
Get under it and give it all you got.
- I don't think we can do this.\N- I'll do 90% of the work.
Just put your weight behind it.
When I say "lift," lift. Ready?
Lift.
Oh!
- Come on. Push!\N- I am pushing!
I bet if there were doughnuts underneath,
you'd be able to flip it.
Fuck you.
Okay.
What exactly is your plan?
This is the narrowest part of the road.\NNo way around.
He'll have to get out\Nof his car to help you.
Help me?
You'll be in the car.
Goddamn it.
What's so funny?
I'm supposed to retire\Nin five months.
I was gonna ride my desk out\Ntill the end of the year,
start hammering pension checks,
but when things went sideways for Duff...
Been with her since she was a boot.
Closest thing to a kid I'll ever have.
Now, I'm like every veteran cop\Nin every cop movie.
Inches from the gold watch,
but I'm gonna get killed when this guy\Ncomes flying around the corner
and plows right into my ass.
He'll hit the brakes\Nas soon as he rounds the corner.
If he's going 70, he'll come\Nto a complete stop in just over 490 feet.
We're 500 feet from the turn.
Ten feet to spare?
That's not much wiggle room.
Odds are he'll be going\Nunder 70 miles an hour on this road.
Promise you'll be fine.\NMath is never wrong.
What if he hits the brakes late?
Do your retirement payments\Ntransfer to your wife?
Asshole.
Shut up. I hear a car.
Shit!
What the hell?
This is for Eliot.
Good work.
I got to get back to Beck before\Nthey send someone to check on me.
Let's throw the guy in the trunk.
Hide the car in the brush.
I'll help you roll it over.
I got it.
I promised the car wouldn't hit you,\Ncan't stop a coronary.
Asshole.
Yes, well, it was a cold case,\Nseveral years old.
He was following up on an anonymous tip
on a Worcester drug ring,\Nand it looks like it was a setup.
Mr. Eliot, I just want you to know,\Nwe are not gonna rest
until we get every person\Nresponsible for what happened.
I-I'm sorry.\NMay I ask your name again, Agent?
Of course. It's Susan Duffy.
I remember.
We met at the Christmas party.
M-Mr. Eliot, I, um...
Earlier today, I was in danger,\Nand Eliot warned me.
He saved my life.
Your son was an excellent agent, sir.
Thank you, Agent Duffy.
Hey.
The man\Nwho killed Eliot is dead.
Good. Now let's get the rest of them.
What will you tell the DEA?
Same bullshit\NI told Eliot's father.
Should buy us some time, not much,
but hopefully enough to find Teresa.
When it's all over, I'll come clean.
It'll cost you your job.
Good. It should.
I owe you a thank-you.
What for?
If you hadn't taken out the lights,\NI could've never left
and Cooper would've come home\Nand I'd be dead.
Saving the life of a good person\Nis a pretty low bar for praise.
Okay.
Pulling up to Beck's now. Be safe.
You stay safe, too, Reacher.
What's going on?
You tell me. What happened out there?
Nothing.
Heard over the radio,\Na drunk hit a power transformer,
took out the lights for half the county.
I didn't mean to cause undue alarm,
but with everything that's been happening,
better safe than sorry.
That's what the boss thought, too.
So, while you were gone,\Nwe searched the entire place.
Your boss is smart.
You find anything? Everything okay?
No.
It's not.
Turns out,
I let someone in my home
that's working with the Feds.
Well, you think you know someone, right?
You invite 'em into your home,
you shelter 'em,
you feed 'em.
You trust them with your family.
And how do they repay you?
With betrayal.
- This was found in the maid's room.\N- What the hell is that?
Some kind of phone.
She was giving out details\Nabout our business--
when the next delivery is happening,
approximate cargo size,
even who's gonna be\Nat my goddamn birthday party.
Fucking Judas was texting her people
every two weeks, and the latest entry
was ten days ago, so we got four days\Nbefore anyone's looking for her.
Who would be looking for her?
Fucking ATF, stupid.
Who else?
McCabe's gonna blame me for this.\NI hired her.
Let me talk to her. I was an M.P.
I know how to interrogate\Nand get information out of people.
If you want to talk to Frenchie,\Nyou're gonna need a Ouija board.
You killed her?
Not me.
I gave her a crack to the head\Nto get her to cooperate.
Oops.
You think that's funny?
Why are you so bent out of shape?\NYou fucking her?
I'm pissed 'cause you killed a source
before I had a chance\Nto get any information.
That's what I said.
It was a dumb move by a dumb man.
Do something about it.
See? It doesn't kill everybody.
Hey, Punch and Judy,\Nwe got work to do.
Move your ass.
Man, he rung your bell like school's out.
I warned you he was coming for you.
You got off lucky.\NHe could have killed your ass.
And I would've had\Nto dump the maid by myself.
By the way, keep your mouth shut
around the house staff\Nabout her being dead.
No one saw anything\Nbecause it happened in the kitchen.
We told everyone she was fired\Nfor stealing from Beck's business.
They don't know shit,\Nand we got to keep it that way.
Power's back.
Bet you feel like a jackass,
thinking someone was\Ngonna come kill us all
when the real danger\Nwas inside the house the whole time?
Go.
Look at what that big idiot did.
Okay, let's go flush her down.
This whole thing really\Nscrewed up my plans, you know?
I got me a boat down in Port Rome\Nthat I'm fixing up, The Sweet Marie.
I was gonna do a little fishing\Non Saturday.
Now that Angel Doll's dead,\NI'm gonna have to write new want ads
for a new maid\Nand upload it to all the job sites.
Barely know how to do that shit.
I'm not Steve Jobs.
Then I'm gonna have to\Ngo through all the résumés.
You know McCabe's\Ngonna be really up my ass
to do background checks on everyone.
This fucking snail-eater\Nreally ruined my weekend.
Good. Found your off switch.
You okay?
I'm fine.
I know you dumped Annette's body\Nin the ocean with Harley.
I had to.
I work for them.
I say "no," I'm the next one in the water.
You're afraid of Paulie.
I'm not afraid of him.
I just haven't solved him yet.
Big guys like that\Naren't usually that fast.
He took me by surprise.
Won't happen again.
It's okay to be scared of these guys.
My dad is.
So am I.
Reacher?
The maid was ATF.
She's gone.
They killed her.
Shit.
You're with DEA, maid's with the ATF.
It's Alphabet City in that place.
They're running guns, not drugs.
It all makes sense.
Beck met with Darien Prado.
International drug runners need lots\Nof high-end, untraceable weapons.
I didn't understand why Beck needed\Na mechanic for barely used cars,
but Quinn needs him to make sure
the weapons are in perfect working order\Nbefore selling 'em.
That's why I found that industrial\Nlubricant company on Angel Doll's laptop.
They purchase the oil in bulk,\Ntest the guns, grease 'em up.
It's white-glove service\Nwhen you buy from Quinn.
That's also why the dog\Ncouldn't sniff anything on that truck.
There were no drugs, just guns.
Quinn has that big sale coming up.
It's gonna be a shitload\Nof illegal firepower.
The question is, for who?
We already know they supply drug dealers.
There are lots of people who'd like\Nto get their hands
on what you saw in that warehouse--
militias, terrorists, warlords, cartels--
any number of buyers\Nfor any number of reasons.
None of 'em good.
You're being quiet.
Was thinking about the maid.
If they killed a Fed\Nwhen they knew she was a Fed,
what the hell could they do to Teresa?
- We've been summoned to the warehouse.\N- We?
Yeah. You and me, specifically.
Did you sleep last night?
No.
Well, an exhausted bodyguard's\Nno use to me.
What the hell is your problem?
No problem.
Let's go.
Reacher?
You still have the maid's blood\Non your hands.
Why don't you wash up\Nand get your shit together?
Hey. What's up?
I don't know exactly what's going on,\Nbut both Beck and I have been
summoned to Bizarre Bazaar.
Only one person has the power to do that.
You're gonna see Quinn.
He wants to talk to you for some reason.
Or maybe we take one step inside\Nhis warehouse
and meet a firing squad for letting\Na federal agent infiltrate his operation.
Well, Beck I get, he hired her.
- But why you?\N- I'm his head of security.
And Quinn's a psychopath.
Don't go.
Don't have a choice.
At least keep the phone on in your pocket.
Villy and I will head over there,\Nstake the place out.
If you get compromised,\Nwe'll head in, back you up.
I'll be surrounded by trained killers.
So, I just leave you in there\Nto get killed?
I don't care what his plans are for me.
I have plans for him.
Negative.
He got past me in Portland and Virginia.
I get near him, it's not happening again.
What, so you kill him\Nand try to shoot your way out?
He could recognize me,\Nand I might not have a choice.
And he might have no idea\Nwho the fuck you are.
He had amnesia, remember?
Maybe he did.
Maybe he faked it.
Reacher, it's suicide. And homicide.
You kill Quinn,\Nthen you're killing Teresa too,
'cause for all we know, Quinn's\Nthe only person who knows where she is.
- Someone on his crew will know.\N- Even if someone in his crew
has her location, they'll likely kill her
after they find out\Nthere's a third infiltrator in the mix.
They'll cut their losses,\Nclean up their mess and move on.
Duffy.
She's already dead.
Fuck you.
They found out the maid was undercover,
and she was dead within minutes.
There's no way they haven't already\Nstarted cleaning up their mess.
She's gone.
You there?
Duffy, I got to go.
I'll leave my phone on.
Shit.
You get called in like this a lot?
No.
McCabe normally comes to my house\Nand walks in and out like it's his.
You think we're gonna\Nwalk in and out today?
Or just in?
I don't know.
Ooh. Here we go.
How's the face?
You ready to meet the boss?
Yes.
I've been waiting for this moment\Nfor some time now.
♪ Can't take no more\Nof this fooling around ♪
♪ Got to go down there\Nand turn up some ground ♪
♪ This old mule, these blades,\Nthese lines on this plow ♪
♪ Gonna work 'em on you,\Ngonna crush you on down ♪
♪ Oh, babe ♪
♪ I'm bound to plow you under ♪
♪ Forget you forever and ever ♪
♪ I'm bound to plow you goddamn under ♪
♪ Nobody wonder where you been, neither ♪
♪ I work hard all day trying\Nto get you off my mind ♪
♪ These old folks down here they say,\N"Son, give it some time" ♪
♪ This burning worried trouble,\Nsorrow all the time ♪
♪ Got a bone to pick, bitch ♪
♪ I'm gonna crush you fucking down ♪
♪ Oh, babe ♪
♪ I'm bound to plow you under ♪
♪ Forget you forever and ever ♪
♪ I'm bound to plow you goddamn under ♪
♪ Nobody wonder where you been, neither ♪
♪ Yeah, this song's about plowing ♪
♪ In case you didn't know ♪
♪ I'm gonna plow a little while ♪
♪ Plow! ♪
♪ The sun is going down ♪
♪ Well, the sun is going down ♪♪